Today is the second day of our Tianping Island trip.
اليوم هو اليوم الثاني في رحلة جزيرة تيانبينغ
Unfortunately, five islanders will be
من المؤسف أن هناك خمسة من سكان الجزيرة
leaving the island.
سيغادرون الجزيرة للأسف
This is so harsh.
يا له من أمر قاسٍ
I can't take it.
لا أحتمل ذلك
My poor heart almost couldn't handle it.
قلبي الصغير كاد يتوقف
I think this is too cruel.
أشعر أنها قاسية جدًا
Seriously, I'm getting real survival vibes.
فعلاً، شعرت وكأنها منافسة للبقاء
Everything is happening too fast.
كل هذا حدث بسرعة كبيرة
We haven't even memorized everyone's names yet.
لم أتمكن حتى من حفظ أسماء الجميع
And now people are already leaving.
ثم بدأ البعض يرحلون فورًا
In this extremely harsh survival environment,
في بيئة البقاء القاسية هذه
the undercurrents between people,
هناك الكثير من التوترات الخفية بين الناس
the intense competition,
منافسة شرسة
are unprecedented.
لم أشهد مثلها من قبل
Nice, a three-person date.
جميل! موعد مع ثلاثة أشخاص
Can I say I like them all?
هل يمكنني القول إني أحب الجميع؟
So much has happened in just 48 hours.
حدث الكثير في أقل من ثمانٍ وأربعين ساعة
I wonder if anyone will leave tomorrow.
لا أدري إن كان هناك مغادرة غدًا
Will there? Probably.
هل هناك؟ ربما نعم
Maybe four to six people.
ربما يكون العدد من أربعة إلى ستة
About four or five.
أربعة أو خمسة تقريبًا
I think there's a good chance I won't be here tomorrow either.
أشعر أنني قد لا أكون هنا غدًا
I didn't vote entirely for any one person.
لم أضع كل رهاني على أي شخص
I balanced the scales again.
لقد أعدت توازن الميزان من جديد
The male contestants I like
الشاب الذي أفضله
might all be in danger.
قد يكون في وضع خطر
I'm saying we should explore more options early on.
أعني في البداية يجب أن أختار أكثر
Going all in on one? I can accept that outcome.
الكل على واحد، أستطيع تقبل النتيجة
I still want to get to know everyone better.
أرغب حقًا في التعرف على الجميع أكثر
Nannan's Chinese name is
اسم نان نان الصيني هو
Hu Wei.
هو وي
It's all about the thrill
اللعبة كلها إثارة وتشويق
Yeah, tomorrow's the moment when life or death is revealed
صحيح، غدًا ستتوضح مصائرنا
May heaven smile upon me
ليت الحظ يكون معي
Let me experience love just once
دعني أعيش قصة حب مرة واحدة فقط
Today is the third day.
اليوم الثالث
The battle is escalating.
التنافس يزداد حماسًا
I never expected the situation to turn out like this today.
لم أكن أتوقع أبدًا أن يكون الوضع هكذا اليوم
The pressure is quite intense.
الضغوط كبيرة
Do you think I'll leave today?
هل تظن أنني سأغادر اليوم؟
They're here
لقد بدأ الأمر
It's starting
انطلقت المنافسة
I really hate this music
أكره هذه الموسيقى جدًا
Good morning, islanders
صباح الخير جميع سكان الجزيرة
The charm point results as of last night
نتائج مؤشر الجاذبية حتى الليلة الماضية
Will be revealed shortly
سيتم الكشف عنها قريبًا
Today, three islanders
اليوم سيغادر ثلاثة من سكان الجزيرة
Will end their Tianping Island adventure
وينهون مغامرتهم في جزيرة تيانبينغ
Three people
ثلاثة
Three will leave the island today
اليوم سيغادر ثلاثة أشخاص
All islanders please pack your belongings
يرجى من الجميع تجهيز أمتعتهم
And gather at the common area quickly
والتجمع بسرعة في منطقة الدردشة
Today, each islander's stay or departure
بقاءكم أو رحيلكم اليوم
Will be determined by charm rankings
يعتمد على ترتيبكم في مؤشر الجاذبية
And your own choices
وكذلك على اختياراتكم الخاصة
Ultimately three will regrettably leave
وفي النهاية سيغادر ثلاثة للأسف
The twelve remaining islanders
الاثنا عشر المتبقون في الجزيرة
Will form four teams of three
سيكوّنون في النهاية أربع فرق من ثلاثة أشخاص
The four team captains
قادة الفرق الأربعة
Will consist of two male
سيكونون شابين
And two female members
وفتاتين أيضاً
Based on accumulated charm points
حسب ترتيب مؤشر الجاذبية التراكمي للجنسين
And your own selections
ومن خلال اختياراتكم كذلك
The four captains will have
سيحصل القادة الأربعة على
Varying degrees of team selection rights
درجات مختلفة من حقوق اختيار الفرق
Islanders who fail to form teams
من لا يستطيع تشكيل فريق
Will bid farewell to Tianping Island
سيودع جزيرة تيانبينغ
I want to stay and celebrate Lu Wanfei's birthday
أريد البقاء للاحتفال بعيد ميلاد لو وانفاي
And get to know them better
وأتعرف قليلاً على البقية أيضاً
I hope I can make it to the end
أتمنى أن أصل للنهاية
Let me experience romance
دعني أعيش قصة حب ولو مرة واحدة
The male contestants I like might be risky choices
الشباب الذين يعجبونني ربما في خطر
I'll try to interact with them more
سأحاول الاقتراب والتعرف عليهم أكثر
I haven't been on a date yet
لم أخرج في موعد بعد
I want to stay
أرغب بالبقاء
And go on a date with Hu Wei
وأواعد هو وي مرة واحدة
First
أولاً
The female with highest charm points
يرجى من الفتاة الأعلى في مؤشر الجاذبية
Hu Wei, step forward
هو وي، تقدم رجاءً
Next,
التالي
The male contestant with the highest accumulated charm points,
يرجى من الشاب الأعلى في مؤشر الجاذبية
Fu Jie, step forward.
فو جيه، تقدم رجاءً
Fu Jie.
فو جيه
Now please, Hu Wei and Fu Jie
الآن، هو وي وفو جيه
From the remaining islanders
من بين بقية سكان الجزيرة
each select any two islanders of the opposite sex
يرجى من كل واحد اختيار شخصين من الجنس الآخر
to form teams
لتكوين فريق معًا
Your charm stat is the highest. Do you want to choose first?
مؤشر جاذبيتك الأعلى، هل تريدين البدء بالاختيار؟
You haven't decided yet, right?
ألم تقرري بعد؟
Have you made up your mind?
هل قررتِ الآن؟
You can choose once you've decided.
إذا قررتِ، يمكنك الاختيار
Hu Wei, please make your choice.
هو وي، الرجاء اختيارك الآن
Congratulations to Hu Wei, Jiang Shangru, and Gu Zhenxiang
مبروك لهو وي، جيانغ شانغرو، غو تشنشيانغ
Team formation successful
تم تكوين الفريق بنجاح
Now please make your choice, Fujie.
الآن فو جيه، يرجى اختيارك
When we teamed up, I wanted to talk with you.
أردت التحدث معك أثناء تشكيل الفرق
But you weren't yourself yesterday.
لكن بالأمس لم تكوني في حالتك
How do you know I wasn't myself?
كيف عرفت أنني لم أكن في حالتي؟
Out of all the guys,
من بين جميع الشباب
I like you the most.
أنت المفضل لدي
Choose your favorite from these
اختاري هنا الشخص الذي تفضلينه
I think you're...
أظن أنني سأختارك
I feel like we really click
أشعر بأني أنسجم معك في الحديث أكثر
Good taste
لديك ذوق جيد
Please make your choice, Fu Jie
فو جيه، يرجى اختيارك الآن
Alright
حسنًا
He should protect me, that's what I think.
أعتقد أنه سيحميني، هذا رأيي
Because we've joked about it before.
لأننا مزحنا معًا من قبل
He could decide whether I stay or go.
بإمكانه أن يقرر بقائي أو رحيلي
Would you choose me?
هل ستختارني؟
He said he would.
قال إنه سيفعل
I choose both of you.
أختاركما أنتما الاثنان
Thank you.
شكرًا
Are you sitting in the middle?
هل ستجلس في المنتصف؟
He didn't choose Chen Mengjia.
لم يختر تشن منغجيا
I choose both of you.
أختاركما أنتما الإثنان
Socially "dead".
لقد أحرجت نفسي اجتماعيًا
So unnatural
غير طبيعي أبدًا
What should I do?
ماذا أفعل الآن؟
I don't even know how to position my legs
لا أعرف حتى أين أضع ساقي
He held hands with the other two female guests
أمسك بيدي الضيفتين الأخريين
I was stunned at that moment
كنت مرتبكة وقتها
My composure completely collapsed
انهارت حالتي النفسية كليًا
In an instant, my beliefs
في لحظة واحدة إيماني كله
Completely shattered
انهار بالكامل
You chose so casually, my dude
اخترت بسهولة شديدة، يا صاح
I
أنا...
You didn't even think
لم تفكر أبدًا
We've already been in a group before
لقد شكّلنا فريقًا من قبل
I believe in you
أنا أثق بك
Alright alright, good work everyone
شكرًا للجميع، بذلتم جهدًا كبيرًا
We've already been paired before
لقد كنا في فريق واحد بالفعل
From these, choose your favorite
اختر من بينهم من تفضله
I think you...
أظن أنك أنت
I feel we have good chemistry in conversation, yes
أعتقد أنني أتناغم معك في الحديث، صحيح
Good taste
ذوقك جيد
Yes, perfect match
نعم، أنتما مناسبين
Off to "get married"
اذهبوا "لتتزوجوا" الآن
Goodbye everyone
وداعًا يا أهلنا
Playing dumb to win big
تُظهر الضعف لكنك قوي
You're not on the waiting list
أنت لست في قائمة الانتظار
I choose both of you
اخترتكما أنتما الإثنان
Attention please
يرجى الانتباه
Islanders who fail to form teams
سكان الجزيرة الذين لم يكوّنوا فريقًا
will have to leave Tianping Island
سيغادرون جزيرة تيانبينغ
Oh no
سيء جدًا
I was truly shocked at that time
كنت فعلاً مصدومًا في ذلك الوقت
Because I never actually thought
لأني لم أفكر في ذلك قط
that Fu Jie would choose Lu Wanfei
أن فو جيه سيختار لو وانفاي
Fu Jie probably knew
ربما يعرف فو جيه
that I had quite a good impression of Lu Wanfei
أن لدي مشاعر إيجابية تجاه لو وانفاي
So I was quite shocked at that time
لذلك كنت مصدومًا فعلاً وقتها
I knew there was a high probability
أعرف أن احتمالي كبير
that I might have to leave the island
بأنني سأغادر الجزيرة
When making team selections
خلال اختيار تشكيل الفرق
I actually didn't realize
لم أكن أدرك حقًا أن
this was connected to leaving the island
هذا مرتبط بمغادرة الجزيرة
My thought at that time
ما فكرت به وقتها
was just wanting to continue with
كان فقط أن أستمر مع زميلي الأمس
the two teammates who performed well yesterday
اللذين كانا رائعين فعلًا
and form a team together again
لأكوّن معهم فريقاً مرة أخرى
But I somewhat regret
لكنني ندمت قليلاً
not choosing Chen Mengjia
لأنني لم أختر تشن منغجيا
According to the recent selection results
بالاستناد للخيارات السابقة
among the remaining male islanders
من بين الشباب الباقين
the one with highest accumulated charm points is
الأعلى في مؤشر الجاذبية هو
Zheng Dedong
تشنغ ديدونغ
Congratulations on becoming the third team captain.
مبروك لك كونك ثالث القادة
Zheng Dedong, please select a resident of the opposite sex.
يرجى من تشنغ ديدونغ اختيار شخص من الجنس الآخر
The selected resident
الشخص الذي يتم اختياره
can then choose another resident of the opposite sex
باستطاعته اختيار شخص آخر من الجنس الآخر
to form a team.
لتشكيل فريق معًا
Please make your choice.
يرجى اختيارك الآن
Xiao Enya.
شياو انيا
I hope to leave behind some
أتمنى أن أستطيع الإبقاء على من
people I want to keep in my life
أرغب بالاستمرار معهم
Let's go
لنذهب
Do I have to choose?
هل يجب أن أختار؟
You must choose.
نعم، عليك أن تختاري
Xiao Ai, please choose one male islander.
يرجى من شياو انيا اختيار شاب من الجزيرة
Guo Xu
غو شيو
Iconic scene
لحظة شهيرة
Congratulations to Zheng Dedong, Xiao Enya, Guo Xu
مبروك لتشنغ ديدونغ، شياو انيا، غو شيو
Team formed successfully
تم تكوين الفريق بنجاح
After spending two days together, to be honest
بعد قضاء يومين معًا، بصراحة
The one I currently have the most favorable impression of is
أشعر بميل أكبر تجاه
My two partners
زميلي الاثنين
Zheng Dedong on the first day
تشنغ ديدونغ في اليوم الأول
Guo Xu on the second day
غو شيو في اليوم الثاني
Based on the recent selection
اعتمادًا على الاختيارات الأخيرة
Among the remaining female islanders
من الفتيات الباقيات في الجزيرة
The one with the highest accumulated charm points is
الأعلى بمؤشر الجاذبية هي
He Jinyi
خه جين يي
Please note
يرجى الانتباه
This is the last round for team formation
هذه آخر فرصة لتشكيل الفرق
Islanders who fail to form a team
الذين لم يتمكنوا من الانضمام لفريق
Will bid farewell to Tianping Island
سأودّع جزيرة تيانبينغ
Please choose carefully
يرجى الاختيار بعناية
Now, He Jinyi, please make your choice
الآن، نرجو من هي جين يي اختيارك
I choose He Jinyi
أختار هي جين يي
Because she was the one who stayed with me yesterday
لأنها كانت معي طوال البارحة
And comforted me
وكانت تواسيني أيضًا
Let's blow them together
دعونا ننفخ معًا
It can't be saved
لا يمكنني حماية ذلك
I might not be able to protect you either
ربما لن أستطيع حمايتك أيضًا
It's okay, I'm still here
لا بأس، أنا هنا معك
Our teamwork was amazing today
انسجامنا اليوم كان مذهلًا
Exactly
هذا صحيح
Don't worry, I'm here.
لا بأس، أنا هنا معك
We had great teamwork today.
انسجامنا اليوم كان مذهلًا
Exactly.
هذا صحيح
When members were being picked one by one,
عندما تم اختيار الأعضاء واحدًا تلو الآخر
I gradually began to realize that he seemed
بدأت تدريجيًا ألاحظ أنه يبدو أنه
to be left out.
بقي وحيدًا
Then when it finally came to
وعندما اختير أخيرًا
Daniel's turn,
دانيال
I pretty much knew
عندها أدركت تقريبًا
Chen Guanyu probably wouldn't be chosen.
أن تشن غوان يو لم يُختر
I shed a few tears -
دمعت عيناي قليلًا
just for a moment.
كان ذلك في لحظة واحدة
It was unexpected.
لم أتوقع هذا
Far beyond expectations.
على بُعد آلاف الأميال
Everyone has their own preferences,
لكل شخص نوعه المفضل
so this was all within
لذا كل هذا يحدث في إطار
uncontrollable circumstances.
عوامل خارج سيطرتنا
I don't regret who I dated
لذلك لا أندم على من واعدت
or spent time with.
أو على من قضيت وقتي معه
Now Daniel, please choose a female islander.
الآن، يرجى من دانيال اختيار إحدى الفتيات
All the pressure is on Daniel now.
كل الضغط بات على دانيال
I choose you
أختارك أنت
Thank you
شكرًا
Congratulations to He Jinyi, Daniel, and Chen Mengjia
مبروك لـ هي جين يي، دانيال، وتشنغ منغ جيا
Team formed successfully
نجحتم في تشكيل فريق
Yes
نعم
Because I think Chen Mengjia's personality
لأنني أرى شخصية تشنغ منغ جيا
is very straightforward and candid
صريحة للغاية وواضحة
I hope we can get to know each other
آمل أن نتعرف على بعضنا
Chen Guanyu
تشن غوان يو
Tao Zhi
تاو تشي
Guan Ziqi
غوان زيتشي
Unfortunately
مؤسف جدًا
You have not successfully remained on the island
لم ينجح بقاؤكم في الجزيرة
Although your journey to Tianping Island has come to an end,
ومع أن رحلتكم في جزيرة تيانبينغ انتهت
we believe your story is far from over.
لكن قصتكم لم تنتهِ بعد
Chen Guanyu was the first person I met here
تشن غوان يو بالنسبة لي
who truly understood me
هو أول من فهمني حقًا
accepted me for who I am
وتقبلني كما أنا
and became a good brother who included me in everything
وكان أخًا جيدًا أمضيت أوقاتًا معه
I never imagined he would leave
لم أتوقع أبدًا أنه سيغادر
When he left
عندما رحل
it felt so sudden
شعرت بأنه كان الأمر مفاجئًا جدًا
completely unexpected
لم أكن أتوقع ذلك أبدًا
Because in this program
لأن في هذا البرنامج
he was like my source of security
كان مصدر الأمان لي نوعًا ما
So when he left
وعندما غادر
I instantly felt so helpless
شعرت بالعجز فجأة
This was truly
أرى أن هذه كانت
a unique experience
تجربة مختلفة تمامًا
that might never happen again
ربما لن تتكرر مرة ثانية
Sorry
آسف
My apologies
عذرًا
Lu Wanfei told me her birthday is April 1st
لو وانفاي أخبرتني أن عيد ميلادها أول أبريل
I regret not having the chance to celebrate with her
وأشعر بالأسف لعدم تمكني من الاحتفال معها
Another regret is
وأشعر أيضًا بالأسف
not getting to know more people
لأنه لم تتح لي فرصة التعرف على المزيد
and hear their stories
واستماع قصصهم
Both same-sex and opposite-sex friendships
سواء كانوا من نفس الجنس أو مختلفين
Because such opportunities are rare
أعتقد أنها تجربة نادرة
I might never have this experience again
وقد لا تتكرر مرة أخرى بالنسبة لي
How could this happen?
كيف حدث هذا؟
Every time before coming, I feel quite open-minded, but...
دائمًا أكون متفائلًا قبل القدوم، لكن...
When it really comes time to say goodbye, it's so
عندما يحين الوداع حقًا، يكون الأمر...
I said I wouldn't cry today
قلت لن أبكي اليوم
How weak of me
لكنني ضعيف
He (Chen Guanyu) is
هو (تشن غوان يو) شخص
truly, I think
أراه حقًا...
the most compatible
الأكثر ملاءمةً لي
who truly understands me
ويفهمني فعلًا
person.
هو ذلك الشخص
Dear island residents
أيها الجزيرة جميعًا
Letters from off-island residents
رسائل من غادروا الجزيرة
have been posted on the bulletin board
تم عرضها على لوحة الإعلانات
You may check them at your convenience
يمكن للجميع الاطلاع عليها
I'll go
سأذهب
You go get them
اذهب أنت وأحضرها
You read it.
اقرأها أنت
I think you should keep this one.
أعتقد أن من الأفضل أن تجعلها لك
This should...
هذا الشيء...
belong to Chen Guanyu.
يخص تشن غوان يو
Thank you to this show
شكرًا لهذا البرنامج
and all the staff for their help
ولكل من عمل هنا وساعدنا
None of this would have happened without you
لولاكم، لم يكن كل هذا ليحدث
I'm so happy to have met
سعدت بالتعرف على
everyone on this journey
كل شخص في هذه الرحلة
and I'm glad you all got to know me
وسعدت أنكم تعرفتم علي
Hello everyone, I'm Chen Guanyu
مرحبًا بالجميع، أنا تشن غوان يو
Guanyu—"Guan" as in observe, "Yu" as in universe
غوان يو، الأول من "المراقبة"، الثاني من "الكون"
Delicious
لذيذ
It actually works
حقًا جيد
Tomorrow, try to secure a spot for the date
حاول أن تحصل على موعد غدًا
Okay, I'll do my best
حسنًا، سأجتهد
So romantic
كم هو رومانسي
Please, have a seat
تفضل بالجلوس
You kept your promise from yesterday
لقد وفيت بوعدك بالأمس
Everyone is so kind
الجميع لطفاء
Each has their own unique charm
ولهم ميزاتهم الخاصة
Not bad
جميل
The law of attraction
قانون الجاذبية
I'm also really happy
وأنا أيضًا سعيدة جدًا
to visit this beautiful island
جئت إلى هذه الجزيرة الجميلة
and spend this extraordinary day
وقضيت يومًا لا يُنسى هنا
Hello everyone, I'm Chen Guanyu.
مرحبًا، أنا تشن غوان يو
I'm twenty-three years old.
عمري ثلاثة وعشرون عامًا
I'm a tennis player.
أنا لاعب تنس
Although it hasn't been many days,
رغم أن الأيام لم تكن كثيرة
it feels like a long time to me.
لكنها بدت لي وكأنها فترة طويلة
It's very different from my life
كانت مغايرة لكل سنوات حياتي الماضية
over the past twenty-plus years.
اختلفت كثيرًا عما عشت
For the past fifteen years,
فقد قضيت خمسة عشر عامًا بفعل شيء واحد
I've been doing the same thing - playing tennis.
هو اللعب المتواصل بالتنس
So for me,
لذا بالنسبة لي بالفعل
this is a very different experience.
كان هذا المكان مختلفًا جدًا
Meeting different people,
وقد التقيت بأشخاص مختلفين تمامًا
whether it's life experiences
سواء التجارب الحياتية
or forming friendships,
أو صداقات جديدة
I've gained significant insights from all of it.
جميعها منحتي الكثير من الدروس
I hope after twelve days,
آمل بعد مضي اثني عشر يومًا
you won't forget that
أن تتذكروا أن
Chen Guanyu appeared on this show.
تشن غوان يو كان موجودًا في هذا البرنامج
Even when leaving, do it with style.
حتى حين الانسحاب، يجب أن أظل أنيقًا
Let me read it for you
دعني أقرأ لك
Will you listen to me?
هل يمكنك أن تستمع فقط؟
Summer has always been my favorite season
الصيف هو فصلي المفضل
Hello everyone, my name is Lu Wanfei
مرحبًا، اسمي لو وانفاي
You can call me Summer
يمكنكم مناداتي "الصيف"
The person I want to invite is Summer, Lu Wanfei
أود دعوة الصيف، لو وانفاي
After meeting you
بعد لقائي بك
It became an even more special season
أصبح هذا الفصل أكثر تميزًا
This is truly touching, really
هذا فعلاً مؤثر للغاية
It's very well written
كتب بشكل رائع
I think it might be because
أظن أنه ربما
he only spent time with me
بقي معي وحدي فقط
that he sacrificed his chance to stay longer
فقد ضحى بفرصته للبقاء أكثر
I feel guilty for not protecting him better
أشعر بتأنيب الضمير إذ لم أحمه بما يكفي
Would you like some cola?
هل تريد شرب الكولا؟
Let me keep this cola bottle as a memento
سأحتفظ بهذه الزجاجة تذكارًا
I think you have a good sense of boundaries
أظن أنك بارع بمعرفة حدودك
Really?
حقًا؟
Thank you
شكرًا
I consider that high praise
هذا مدح كبير لي
My birthday is April 1st
عيد ميلادك في الأول من أبريل
Try your best to celebrate my birthday with me
حاول أن تحتفل معي بعيد ميلادي
Okay
حسنًا
I'll do my best
سأجتهد حقًا
April 1st birthday
عيد ميلادك في الأول من أبريل
Try your best to celebrate my birthday with me
حاول أن تحتفل معي بعيد ميلادي
Okay
حسنًا
Hello everyone, my name is Tao Zhi.
مرحبًا، اسمي تاو تشي
I'm 27 years old.
أنا في السابعة والعشرين من عمري
Currently, I'm pursuing my Ph.D. at Nanjing University.
أتابع حاليًا الدكتوراه في جامعة نانجينغ
I'm a science student.
أنا طالب علوم
My main research focuses on
مجال بحثي الأساسي هو
radar variable simulation and numerical model simulation.
محاكاة متغيرات الرادار والنمذجة الرقمية
I'm truly grateful to have met them,
ممتن جدًا لأنني التقيت بهم
and deeply honored
وأشعر بالفخر أيضًا
to have had the chance to interact with them.
أن أكون قد تواصلت معهم
It's also regrettable that I didn't get the opportunity
وأشعر بالحزن أيضًا لأنه لم تتسنَ لي فرصة
to have more exchanges with Lu Wanfei
التواصل أكثر مع لو وانفاي
or to know her better.
والتعرف عليها أكثر
It's genuinely quite disappointing.
حقاً أنا آسف لذلك
I feel quite unwilling about it,
ولا أزال غير راضٍ
and rather disheartened.
وأشعر بإحباط إلى حد ما
I keep wondering—if I could’ve stayed a few more days,
أشعر أنه لو بقيت بضعة أيام أخرى
would there have been more unique
لربما كانت هناك تجارب مختلفة أكثر
and beautiful experiences?
وتجارب أجمل بكثير
This was written by classmate Guan Ziqi
هذا من كتابة زميلتنا قوان زي تشي
Everyone has been kinder than I could have imagined
كل شخص هنا أفضل مما تخيلت
If anyone comes to Singapore in the future, you can come find me to hang out
إذا زرتم سنغافورة لاحقًا تعالوا لزيارتي
Until we meet again if fate allows
إلى لقاء آخر إذا جمعنا القدر
Hello everyone
مرحبًا جميعًا
My name is Guan Ziqi
اسمي قوان زي تشي
I'm 21 years old
عمري واحد وعشرون عامًا
Currently studying at National University of Singapore
أنا الآن في جامعة سنغافورة الوطنية
Majoring in Finance
أدرس تخصص المالية
To be honest, I've never experienced
بصراحة لم أختبر أبدًا
this kind of lifestyle before
هذه الطريقة من الحياة
But I feel that
لكنني أرى أن
this kind of lifestyle
هذه الطريقة في العيش
makes me particularly happy
جعلتني أحبها كثيرًا
Guan Ziqi courageously wins the Island Survival Challenge championship
قوان زي تشي تفوز بلقب ساحة البقاء
It's like you've left reality
يشعرك أنك انفصلت عن الواقع
and entered into
ودخلت إلى
a dreamlike state
عالم يشبه الحلم
Although the conditions in this dream are tough
رغم أن هذا الحلم ظروفه صعبة
it makes you feel wonderful and happy
إلا أنه جميل ويمنحك السعادة
Don't be sad anymore
لا تحزن أكثر من هذا
Come out, it's time to come out
اخرج، حان وقت الخروج
Can't move on
لا أستطيع الخروج
We're out
خرجتُ الآن
Dear islanders
أيها سكان الجزيرة
All four teams have assembled
تم تجميع الفرق الأربعة
Today you'll operate as teams
اليوم ستمثلون فرقكم
Team competition
وتتعاونون كفريق
I think your group seems quite stable
أظن أن فريقكم هذا متماسك
What's stable?
متماسك كيف؟
Your team
أنتم في هذا الفريق
Triangles are the most stable shape
المثلث هو الشكل الأكثر استقرارًا
We're truly evenly matched
نحن فعلاً متكافئون بقوة
That's a great name
الاسم رائع
Perfectly named
اختيار موفق فعلاً
Game black hole
ثقب أسود في الألعاب
Yes, you're the black hole
نعم، أنت الثقب الأسود
You're the most "zen" one
أنت الأكثر هدوءًا هنا
Can we win just once?
هل يمكننا مرة أن
The right to choose dates
نختار حق موعد بأنفسنا
Okay?
موافقة؟
Yes, give it to us
نعم، أعطونا ذلك
Actually, I think...
في الحقيقة برأيي
Okay
حسنًا
Alright
تمام
I'll do my best
سأبذل جهدي
Haven't won in two days
لم نفز منذ يومين
I refuse to believe we can't win today
لا أصدق أننا قد نخسر اليوم أيضًا
What game is this anyway?
ما اللعبة هذه المرة؟
All islanders please organize by teams
يرجى من الجميع البقاء مع فرقهم
Choose your tents
واختيار الخيمة بأنفسكم
Same gender pairs share one
شخصان من نفس الجنس في خيمة
The remaining opposite gender gets their own
والآخر المختلف وحده في خيمة
How should we divide the tents?
كيف سنقسم الخيام إذًا؟
Rock paper scissors
حجر ورقة مقص
Grab it, go!
اسحبها، خذها!
Take it, go!
اسحب، خذها!
But yours really...
لكن بالفعل أنتم...
No, it's quite good.
لا، كل شيء جيد
Our dorm is quite nice.
غرفتنا رائعة
It's good.
جميلة
I think our dorm is really fun.
غرفتنا ممتعة برأيي
Right.
نعم
I think so too.
وأنا أيضًا أوافق
Fair competition.
منافسة عادلة
Everyone coexists peacefully.
الجميع يتعايش بسلام
It is fair.
حقًا هذا عادل
I really like you three.
أنا حقًا أحبكم أنتم الثلاثة
Doesn't this scene look like...
ألا تشبه هذه اللحظة
Yesterday, the day before.
البارحة أو قبلها
Be careful
انتبهوا
I'm never wearing these shoes again
لن أرتدي هذا الحذاء أبدًا
Then let's go that way, okay?
إذًا لنذهب هناك، حسنًا؟
Let me carry your bag
دعني أحمل حقيبتك
Bag
الحقيبة
Let's go
هيا بنا
This is too heavy
هذا ثقيل جدًا
It's fine, it's not that heavy
لا بأس، ليس ثقيلًا هكذا
You take another trip first
ارجع مرة ثانية بعدها خذ الباقي
It's alright
لا بأس
You're his benefactor
أنت أنقذتَه
He's repaying you
هو يرد لك الجميل
Then you're my benefactor
إذًا أنت أنقذتني
You have to repay me
عليك رد الجميل لي
What's this? We're the brother squad
ماذا؟ نحن فريق الإخوة
My charm stat is terrible
مؤشر جاذبيتي ضعيف جدًا
Go away
ابتعد
Very beautiful
جميلة جدًا
Prince, your clothes
أيها الأمير، ثيابك
What's wrong?
ماذا بها؟
Your clothes are already wet
ثيابك قد ابتلت بالفعل
No, I think we're ridiculous
لا، أعتقد أننا مضحكون
Coming back to this place again
عدنا لهذا المكان مجددًا
Be careful
انتبه
Thank you, Fang Xu
شكرًا لك قو شيو
Let me get our three bags
سآخذ حقائبنا الثلاثة
Then I'll get his small case
سآخذ له الحقيبة الصغيرة
Can you lift it?
يمكنك حملها؟
No, it's a bit difficult
لا، يبدو الأمر صعبًا
I'll do it
سأتولى ذلك
I'll help you carry them
سأحملها عنكم
If I weren't injured, I could do it
لو لم أكن مصابًا لفعلت
It's okay
لا بأس
Then I'll go with you
سأذهب معك إذًا
Don't you lift it
لا تتحدث عن الأمر
The most reliable man in the universe
أكثر رجل جدير بالثقة في الكون
We're so lucky
نحن محظوظان بالفعل
He looks like he's carrying a chick
يبدو كأنه يحمل دجاجة صغيرة
Just lifts it up
رفعها هكذا ببساطة
Yes, he just looks
نعم، فعلاً يبدو
Very relaxed, and then
بكل سهولة ثم...
I thought the case he was carrying was light
ظننت أن حقيبته خفيفة
So they sleep there?
هل سينامون هناك إذًا؟
Yes
نعم
Right?
أليس كذلك؟
Then let's go over there
إذًا فلنذهب نحن هناك
It's fine, let's go, it's fine
لا بأس، هيا، لا بأس
I still have things
ما زال لدي شيء آخر
And that case too
وأيضًا تلك الحقيبة
There are still things inside
يوجد شيء بالداخل أيضًا
Then I'll move it over first
سأنقل أشيائي أولًا إذًا
I still have things inside
لدي المزيد بالداخل
Then you help her carry it
إذًا ساعدها بحملها
I'll move it first
سأنقل أولا
Having fun?
هل كان ممتعًا؟
Life, life...
هكذا هي الحياة
How did things suddenly turn out like this?
كيف تغير كل شيء فجأة هكذا؟
It's so sunny.
الشمس حارقة
Hurry up, you two.
أنتم الاثنان أسرعوا
Is this your suitcase?
هذه حقيبتك؟
This is that...
هذه تخص...
Hu Wei's.
هو وي
Let me first...
سأعطي الوقت أولًا...
The other male guest...
للشاب الآخر
Let him have his moment first.
دعه يظهر قوته أولًا
Let's go up here.
لنصعد من هنا
Is my suitcase heavy?
هل حقيبتي ثقيلة؟
Is the suitcase heavy?
هل الحقيبة ثقيلة؟
No, it's okay.
لا، عادية
Is there one more?
هل بقيت واحدة؟
No.
لا
None left?
هل لم يبق شيء؟
So I don't know what game we'll play this afternoon.
لا نعرف ما هي لعبة اليوم بعد الظهر
I think it will be a cruel game.
أظنها ستكون لعبة قاسية
Cruel?
قاسية؟
Can you not make me suffer more cruelty?
هل يمكن ألا أتحمل القسوة مجددًا؟
I've endured cruelty for two days already.
تحملت القسوة يومين بالفعل
My hand hasn't healed yet.
يدي لم تشفَ بعد
Then I think it's okay to lose.
أظن أنه لا بأس إن خسرنا
No.
لا يمكن
I don't like losing.
أنا لا أحب الخسارة
Alright, then we'll win.
حسنًا، سنفوز إذًا
I originally wanted to say losing doesn't matter.
كنت أظن أن الخسارة لا بأس بها
But...
لكن...
Since she said we must win, then we can only win.
بما أنها تريد الفوز، فلا خيار إلا أن نربح
So I can't be second, I must be first.
لذا لا أقبل أن أكون الثاني، فقط الأول
I'll go get the luggage.
سأحضر الحقائب الآن
Is there anything else?
هل بقي شيء؟
Do you have any?
وأنت، هل لديك شيء؟
I'll rest a bit more.
سأستريح قليلًا
Okay.
حسنًا
Although you mentioned that scale
مع أنكِ تقصدين تلك الكفة
it will only tip to one side.
أنتِ تميلين دائمًا لجانب واحد
Right.
صحيح
Right, I don't know which side.
صحيح، لا أعرف أي جانب
Right, on Balance Island you must choose a side.
نعم، في جزيرة تيانبينغ لا بد أن تختار جانبًا
The scale has already tipped.
الكفة أسقطت بالفعل
Okay.
تمام
Brilliant, really.
رائع، فعلًا
You mean today?
تعنين اليوم؟
Yes.
نعم
So scary.
مخيف جدًا
Today I really wanted to say
كنت اليوم حقًا أفكر في قول
just call my name and let's go.
نادوا اسمي فقط وسأغادر
Let's set off.
فلننطلق فقط
So eager to leave?
ترغبين بالمغادرة لهذا الحد؟
It's not that I want to leave, but...
لست أريد المغادرة، بل
How should I put it...
كيف أقولها...
I feel yesterday was the only time
أظن أن البارحة على هذه الجزيرة
since coming to this island
هي المرة الوحيدة
that I felt completely unconfident.
التي شعرت فيها بانعدام الثقة تمامًا
I was timid, truly afraid.
كنت خائفة جدًا ومترددة
Because I had already
لأني بالفعل
prepared for the worst possible outcome.
كنت مستعدة للأسوأ
Did you ever consider that
هل فكرت يومًا أنه ربما...
in the worst case scenario,
ماذا لو، مجرد احتمال
right? What if I didn't choose you?
ماذا لو لم أخترِكِ؟
Would you then choose another girl
هل ستختارين فتاة أخرى فقط للبقاء؟
just to survive?
ستختارين واحدة أخرى إذًا؟
I'd go all in.
الكل على واحد
I'd give everything (to one person).
سأعطي كل شيء لشخص واحد
Everything.
كل شيء له/لها
You'd rather leave, is that it?
تفضلين الرحيل إذًا؟
So if by chance I didn't choose you,
ماذا لو لم أخترِكِ
and you had to leave the island, what then?
وغادرتِ جزيرة تيانبينغ، ماذا ستفعلين؟
I would...
أنا فقط
just go all in.
سأضع كل الرهان على واحد
I'd go all in.
الكل على واحد
But I...
لكنني...
Actually I shouldn't tell you this,
لا يجب أن أخبرك هذا حقًا
because I don't want to pressure you.
لأنني لا أريد أن أضغط عليك
Really.
صدقًا
You told me
أنتِ قلتِ لي من قبل
you wouldn't feel pressured.
لن أشعر بأي ضغط
What others tell me
ما يقوله الآخرون لي
won't affect my decisions
لن يؤثر على قراري
Okay
حسنًا
I rely heavily on my gut feelings to respond
دائمًا أجيب حسب إحساسي في اللحظة
I am a
أنا شخص...
200% hopeless romantic
عقلي كله غارق في الحب مئتين بالمئة
That's why I'm hesitant to
لهذا لا أجرؤ على...
casually start relationships
الدخول في علاقة بسهولة
Because I feel I fall too easily
لأني أقع بسرعة
In this very moment
في هذه اللحظة تحديدًا
my feelings for this person
مشاعري تجاه هذا الشخص
intensify rapidly
تزداد بسرعة كبيرة
The two of us
نحن الاثنان...
I need a moment
أحتاج لبعض الوقت للهدوء
One of yours left
أنت فقدت واحدًا
All of mine are gone
أما أنا، فقد رحل الجميع
What do you mean all?
كيف كلهم؟
They've all left
كلهم رحلوا
Zhang Xin
تشانغ شين
Tao Zhiquan left
تاو تشي رحل أيضًا
I have nothing else
ليس لدي أحد غيره
Just my steadfast guy now
كنت واثقة باختياري له فقط
Alright
حسنًا
Tao Zhi left today
تاو تشي غادر اليوم
People leave every day, just when we get familiar
دائمًا أحد يغادر، وفقط بدأنا التعرف
Just when you start to understand someone
ما إن أشعر أني فهمت أحدهم
Then they leave
حتى يرحل فجأة
I used to feel protected by him
كنت أشعر أنه يحميني دائمًا
Now he's gone
ثم اختفى
I'm feeling all mixed up inside
قلبي ممتلئ بمشاعر مختلطة
And then...
ثم...
Let's eat then.
فلنأكل إذًا
Let's eat.
لنتناول الطعام
Finally, we get to see some meat.
أخيرًا سنرى اللحم
There's meat today.
اليوم يوجد لحم
Alright, let's dig in.
تمام، بسم الله
Eat more, Fang Xu.
كل أكثر يا قو شو
Their portions are too small.
هذه الكمية قليلة جدًا
This is all just for you.
كل هذا حصة فردية لك فقط
Right?
أليس كذلك؟
Why does today's meal feel a bit...
لماذا الأكل اليوم يبدو
...strange?
شعور غريب حقًا
Every meal from now on feels a bit odd.
من الآن، الأكل سيبقى غريبًا يوميًا
Look how intense it is over there.
انظر للطرف الآخر، هم متحمسون جدًا
That looks fun.
هناك حقًا ممتع
Eat.
كلوا
Don't hold back.
لا تترددوا
I'm really hungry.
أنا جائع فعلاً
I've lost my appetite.
لا شهية لدي
Eat quickly.
كل بسرعة
Or you won't have energy for this afternoon.
وإلا في المساء لن أقدر أن أنافس
I never have energy, every single day.
كل يوم لا أستطيع المنافسة
I feel hopeless before every match.
قبل أن أتنافس أشعر باليأس
I genuinely have no strength.
ليس لدي طاقة أبدًا
It's fine, you don't need to perform today.
لا بأس، اليوم لستَ بحاجة لتقديم شيء
Really?
حقًا؟
Really.
حقًا
Can you reach it?
هل يمكنك الوصول؟
I can reach it.
يمكنني الوصول
Looking down on me?
تستهين بي
Seems like it.
يبدو كذلك
You can't reach it, can you?
أظنك لا تستطيع الوصول
You take some first.
خذ أولاً
That's enough.
يكفي
Being "served" like this by two guys
شخصان يخدمانكِ هكذا
Don’t you think it’s too much pressure?
ألا تشعرين أن الضغط كبير؟
I’ll keep some distance first.
سأبقى على بعض المسافة أولاً
I think we should relax a bit.
أعتقد علينا الاسترخاء
Let’s keep some space.
لنحافظ على بعض المسافة
We can’t go overboard.
لا يجوز أن يكون الأمر مبالغًا فيه
Otherwise, it’d be awkward, right?
وإلا ستشعرين بعدم الراحة، صحيح؟
Let me tell you—this is the variety show version of *Burn in Winter*.
سأحدثك عن نسخة البرنامج من "شتاء مشتعل"
Is this tasty?
هل هذا لذيذ؟
This is okay.
هذا مقبول.
This chicken is decent.
الدجاج جيد.
I'm just mechanically stuffing food into my mouth.
أنا أتناول الطعام وكأنني آلة فقط.
Please, no more tug-of-war this afternoon.
أتوسل، لا نلعب شد الحبل مرة أخرى ظهرًا.
I'm absolutely exhausted.
أنا حقاً متعب جدًا.
They're so strong.
هم أقوياء جداً.
You know, I knew from the very beginning.
تعلم؟ منذ البداية أنا كنت أعرف.
Everyone would assume I'm strong.
الجميع سيظن أنني قوي.
But deep down I understood.
لكنني أعي في داخلي.
My training regimen.
أسلوب تدريبي
wasn't designed for this kind of event.
لا يناسب هذا النوع من المنافسات.
So I was bound to fail.
لذلك أنا لن أستطيع.
At first I thought he was super tough.
ظننت في البداية أنه قوي جدًا.
Turns out he's just a "funny guy."
لكن اتضح أنه شخص مضحك.
That finishing remark.
تعليق جارح.
I ate a bit too much.
أكلت كثيرًا.
I'm off.
سأنسحب الآن.
Did you do your undergrad in China?
هل درست البكالوريوس هنا في البلاد؟
Yes.
نعم.
In Beijing.
درست في بكين.
So you're very familiar with Beijing.
إذًا أنت تعرف بكين جيدًا؟
I only moved within one specific area.
أنا أتنقل فقط في منطقة محددة.
The kind who's never been anywhere else.
لم أزر أي أماكن أخرى.
I don't like it.
لا أحب ذلك.
Too many people, too much pressure.
الكثير من الناس، ضغط كبير.
It feels suffocating.
أشعر بالاختناق بذلك.
So you usually...
إذًا عادةً أنت
find pleasure in solitude?
تفضل الاستمتاع بنفسك وحدك؟
You can do many interesting things alone.
الوحدة تعطيك فرصة لتجربة أشياء ممتعة.
I really enjoy going out alone.
أحب الخروج لوحدي كثيرًا.
Traveling solo.
السفر منفردًا.
Every trip feels like an adventure.
أشعر أن كل رحلة هي مغامرة.
That's the feeling.
فعلاً، هذا هو الإحساس.
I often go out alone too.
أنا أيضًا أخرج وحدي كثيرًا.
I feel like only when I'm alone...
أعتقد أنه فقط حين أكون وحدي
can I truly...
يمكنني حقًا
experience certain things.
أن أشعر ببعض الأمور.
Very free.
أشعر بحرية كبيرة.
Anyway, I feel very free when alone.
على أي حال، الوحدة تريحني وتمنحني حرية.
Yes, exactly.
نعم، صحيح.
And as I grow older...
والآن مع تقدمني في العمر
the more I prefer being alone.
أزداد تقديراً للوحدة.
This is just human...
هكذا هم البشر.
normal...
طبيعي جدًا.
perfectly normal...
هذا أمر طبيعي.
part of the aging process.
نعم، جزء من التقدم بالعمر.
Spending this day with Fujie...
اليوم وأنا مع فو جيه
I discovered many...
اكتشفت فيه الكثير من
other charms beneath his surface.
الجاذبية العميقة خلف مظهره.
A day with him...
قضيت يومًا معه
made me feel that...
وجعلني أشعر أن فيه
there's something very attractive about his inner self.
جوانب داخلية جذابة.
It makes me want to know him better.
وأرغب أن أتعرف عليه أكثر.
I'll have a chicken wing.
سأتناول جناح الدجاج.
These are chicken feet.
هذه رجل الدجاج.
There are still two pieces of meat left, aren't there?
أليس هناك قطعتان من اللحم أيضًا؟
I don't eat that, it's too fatty.
لا أريدها، إنها دهنية جدًا.
You should rinse it first before eating.
اغسلها قبل أن تأكلها.
I need to soak up some oil.
أحاول تصفية الزيت منها.
This is how I usually eat when dining out.
دائمًا أتناول الطعام بهذه الطريقة خارج المنزل.
You're so strict with yourself.
صارم جدًا مع نفسك.
Yes, for decades.
نعم، منذ عشرات السنين.
Years have passed like a single day.
عدة سنوات بنفس الروتين.
Then I eat river snail noodles every day.
إذن أنا أتناول نودلز اللؤلؤ يوميًا.
So stinky.
رائحتها كريهة.
So fragrant.
لكنها لذيذة جداً!
I've never tried it, not once in my life.
لم أذقها بحياتي كلها.
Extremely fragrant.
رائحتها رائعة جدًا!
Then I can use it to stink up your place.
يمكن استخدامها لزعجكم بالرائحة.
I've never had it.
أنا لم أجربها.
Didn't someone bring river snail noodles?
ألم يجلب أحدهم نودلز اللؤلؤ؟
Can we ask them to make it?
هل يمكنه تحضيرها لنا؟
After making it, we'll leave it in your room overnight.
ضعها بغرفتكم ليلةً كاملة بعد الطهي.
How much perfume would we need
كم من العطر يجب استخدامه
to cover up that smell?
لتغطية تلك الرائحة؟
Actually, I brought perfume.
معذرة، أحضرت عطري الخاص.
I brought two bottles.
أحضرت زجاجتين.
What perfume did you bring?
ما نوع العطر الذي لديك؟
Let me see what your taste is like.
دعني أرى ذوقك.
My favorite perfume.
عطري المفضل.
It smells wonderful.
رائحته جميلة.
That shows that you
هذا يكشف عن الشخصية
prefer a certain type of everyday feeling.
وعن ذوقك اليومي.
I'm very
أمتلك الكثير من
Very what?
ماذا أيضًا؟
Stylish, very stylish.
"ستايل خاص"، عندي ستايل.
Someone said I have style, I'm very stylish.
يقول البعض أنني أمتلك ستايلًا.
When I sleep at night,
عندما أنام ليلاً،
I must light aromatherapy and listen to soft music.
أشعل الشموع العطرية وأسمع موسيقى هادئة.
Then have a glass of red wine before bed.
ثم كأس نبيذ صغير للنوم.
That made me laugh.
أضحكتني حقًا.
What's so funny?
لماذا تضحك؟
Wouldn't have guessed.
لا أستطيع أن ألاحظ ذلك.
Bro, you're amazing.
أنت رائع يا أخي.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Fang Xu is very enthusiastic.
غو شيو شخص نشيط جدًا.
He's on the same wavelength as me.
هو على نفس موجتي.
When we talk,
عندما نتحادث
we just understand each other.
نفهم بعضنا بسرعة.
Of course, I do have some affection for him.
أشعر بتقدير خاص تجاهه.
It depends on whether
ولكن هذا يعتمد على
this affection can develop into something deeper.
إذا تحول هذا التقدير لمشاعر أقوى لاحقاً.
This tofu is pretty good.
هذا التوفو جيد.
Really?
صحيح؟
That's because I was the one who served it to you.
لأنني أنا وضعت لكم القطعة.
I genuinely haven't eaten anything this...
صار لي زمن طويل لم أذق شيئا بهذا
delicious in a long time.
الطعم الرائع.
What we had for lunch yesterday was similar.
تناولنا شيئًا مشابهًا البارحة ظهراً.
I didn't get to eat yesterday because...
أنا لم أتناوله ظهر أمس
it was too far.
فقد كان بعيدًا جدًا.
Too much distance.
المسافة بعيدة.
I want some iced cola.
أرغب بكولا مثلجة.
We had some yesterday.
شربنا كولا البارحة.
I know.
أعلم ذلك.
If we complete any missions successfully today,
إذا ربحنا مهمة اليوم
let's get some more.
لنذهب وأحضر منها.
Mhm.
حسنًا.
I saw in their supply room...
رأيت في غرفة الموارد الخاصة بهم
there's a wine set,
مجموعة كؤوس نبيذ.
but no actual wine.
لكن ليس هناك نبيذ.
Right.
صحيح.
We can just hold the glasses and pretend.
نحمل الكؤوس ونتظاهر أننا نشرب.
We could use them for iced cola!
يمكننا استخدام الكأس لكولا مثلجة.
We still have ice cubes.
لدينا مكعبات ثلج أيضًا.
Then we'll wear our fanciest clothes,
نرتدي أجمل ثيابنا
carry the glasses around on patrol,
ونتجول حاملين الكؤوس.
and toast everyone.
نحيي الجميع بكأس!
He Jinyi...
خه جين يي
I hope we can take things slower.
أرغب بأن أتحرك معها بوتيرة أبطأ قليلًا.
Because I think...
لأني أعتقد
we've been moving too fast these days.
الأيام الماضية كانت الوتيرة سريعة.
Our relationship progressed too quickly.
تقدمنا بسرعة نوعًا ما.
I hope we can take more time to understand each other
أتمنى أن نتعرف أكثر على بعضنا البعض.
before making any decisions.
ثم نقرر بعدها.
The Survival Arena will open in the afternoon
ساحة البقاء ستفتح بعد الظهر.
All islanders, please be prepared
يرجى من جزيرة تيانبينغ الاستعداد.
Hello
مرحبًا.
Come in
تفضل بالدخول.
I'm going on a date with a guy.
سأذهب لمواعدة أحد الشباب.
Guess who it is.
تخمنوا من الذي سأختاره؟
Fu Jie.
فو جيه.
For several days in a row,
لبضعة أيام، أنت دائمًا
you've been choosing him.
تخاطرين من أجله.
But when it came to deciding your fate,
لكن عندما يصبح الأمر مصيريًا
he didn't choose you.
هو لم يختارك وقت القرار.
Would you still go after him?
هل ستختارينه مجددًا؟
You mean Fu Jie?
تقصدين فو جيه؟
Right, I don't want to do that anymore.
نعم، لا أرغب بتكرار ذلك.
I think it's pointless.
الأمر فقد جاذبيته بنظري.
Then you should ask Gu Zhenxiang out.
قومي بمواعدة غو زينشيانغ إذًا.
Right, I'll ask Gu Zhenxiang.
نعم، سأتواعد مع غو زينشيانغ.
Gu Zhenxiang.
غو زينشيانغ.
The reason I'm asking Gu Zhenxiang is because
سبب اختياري لغو زينشيانغ هو
on the first day's event, we were in the same team.
كنّا فريقًا في أول يوم نشاط.
And he's very gentlemanly,
وهو شخص محترم جدًا.
he takes good care of girls.
يهتم بالفتيات كثيرًا.
Yes, he's quite good.
نعم، هو جيد فعلًا.
So I think he's pretty nice.
لذلك أراه مناسبًا جدًا.
And he's not the kind of person
وأيضًا ليس من النوع
who's boring.
الممل.
With some people, when you chat with them,
بعض الأشخاص عندما تتكلم معهم
if the conversation doesn't flow, it feels exhausting.
تجد الحوار معهم مرهقًا وصعبًا.
Right.
صحيح.
Yes.
أجل.
Gu Zhenxiang is alright too.
غو زينشيانغ جيد أيضًا.
Gu Zhenxiang is currently
حاليًا غو زينشيانغ
completely infatuated with Hu Wei.
مفتون جدًا بـ هو وي.
You know they're taking turns
تعرف أنهم كل يوم
two guys accompanying Hu Wei every day.
شابان يتناوبان على مرافقة هو وي.
Divine map
صورة رائعة.
Looks good
جميلة جدًا.
Won't show you
لن أريك إياها.
Just one glance
دعني أنظر فقط ثانية واحدة.
Got it
فهمت الآن.
From this angle
من هذا الزاوية.
Starting to act
بدأ يتظاهر الآن.
Quite nice
جميلة جدًا فعلاً.
I took a really good shot
صورتها رائعة من عندي.
Let me see it
أرني ثانية واحدة فقط.
Just a second, a quick glimpse
ثانية واحدة، بسرعة البرق.
Want some iced Americano?
هل ترغب بكأس قهوة مثلجة؟
Still has ice cubes
فيه مكعبات ثلج أيضًا.
Only this much for now
جهّز القليل أولاً.
I was gonna say
كنت أريد أن أقول أيضًا...
How does it feel sharing a tent with Gu Zhenxiang?
ما إحساسك أن تعيش مع غو زينشيانغ في خيمة واحدة؟
Asking me?
تسألني أنا؟
Your question is tricky
سؤالك معقد حقًا.
All I can say is
لا أستطيع قول سوى
The dynamic is... delicate
العلاقة بيننا دقيقة جدًا.
Look
شوف
The sunscreen is exactly the same
واقي الشمس نفسه بالضبط
It works really well, right?
ممتاز صح؟
Probably
يبدو كذلك
Okay
تمام
Help me spray some
رشلي شوي
Spray the back of this
رش هنا من الخلف
Just spray the neck
رش على الرقبة فقط
Got it
تمام
What is this?
ما هذا؟
Even our perfumes are the same
حتى عطورنا نفسها
That's too crazy
مستحيل فعلاً
Look at our perfumes
شوف عطورنا الاثنين
Our perfumes are the same
عطرنا نفسه بالضبط
Can't tell the difference anymore
ما أقدر أفرق بينهم
And they're almost used up, you know
واستخدمناه بنفس القدر تقريباً
They're exactly the same
نفسه بالضبط
Right
صح
It's just absurd
شيء غريب فعلاً
She closes her eyes and sniffs
تغمض عينيها وتشتم
And then—both are identical
انتهى الأمر، كلنا نفس الشيء
Dramatic
دراما
Dreamlike
خيال
Such a peculiar combination
توليفة دقيقة جداً
Hu Wei
هو وي، تفضلي
Fu Jie
فو جيه
Daniel
دانيال
Xiao Enya
شاونيا
Proceed to the Survival Arena
توجهوا إلى ساحة البقاء
Shall we go? Together?
نذهب معاً؟
Let's go
هيا بنا
So we're different
يعني نحن مختلفون
Look
شوف
Right, we're each our own team
صح، كل واحد منا بفريق
Wait, does this mean we've become captains?
انتظر، هل صرنا قادة فرق؟
Automatically promoted to captain
ترقينا تلقائياً إلى قادة
It's strange, I'm not smart enough
غريب، أنا ذكائي ضعيف
What?
ماذا؟
She says she's not smart enough
تقول أن ذكاءها ضعيف
No worries, I'm definitely worse
لا بأس، أكيد أنا أضعف
Look, what's this?
ما هذا برأيك؟
What's it for?
ما الغرض منه؟
We're not flipping tires today, are we?
مو اليوم نقلب عجلات صح؟
Drawing?
رسم؟
It can't be that...
أكيد مو هذا
You know, that game where you act and I guess?
لعبة الإشارات والتخمين؟
I'm really good at this game, honestly.
أنا قوي جداً بهذه اللعبة بصراحة
Are you better at acting or guessing?
قوي بالإشارة أم التخمين؟
Both.
الاثنين
I'm no good at either.
أنا ضعيف في كليهما
Why are there locks?
لماذا يوجد قفل أيضاً؟
What's this for?
ما المطلوب بهذا؟
Are they going to lock us up?
راح يقفلون علينا؟
This is insane, absolutely insane.
مجنون فعلاً، لا يصدق
So our teammates are coming to rescue us.
فلازم فريقنا ينقذنا
Let's call it "Rescue of Love," I think.
أسميه إنقاذ المحبة
We're stretched too thin right now.
ما عاد أقدر أتصرف الآن
We can barely protect ourselves.
أحمي نفسي بصعوبة
Help!
النجدة!
Save us!
ساعدونا!
Save me!
أنقذوني
Why haven't they come to save us yet?
ليش ما جاؤوا ينقذونا؟
Attention all island residents,
انتباه يا سكان الجزيرة
the Survival Arena is now open.
ساحة البقاء أصبحت مفتوحة الآن
Everyone must proceed there immediately.
يرجى التوجه فوراً
Let's go.
انطلاق!
It's locked
مقفلين
Hurry up and save me
أنقذوني بسرعة
My feet are tied too
حتى قدمي مربوطة
Right
صح
We need the key
نحتاج مفتاح
You guys come save me
تعالوا أنقذوني
I'll save you
أنا رح أنقذك
My bro came to save me, thanks
أخو يصير وينقذني، شكراً
Kick the shuttlecock
نلعب كرة الريشة
You probably need to
لازم تلعبون
Play the games one by one
كل لعبة واحدة تلو الأخرى
Then you can unlock one
وبعدها تفتحون القفل
It's probably a puzzle, look
أظن لازم تركيب أحجية، شوفوا
Maybe after you complete a task
يمكن بعد انتهاء كل مهمة
I can free one of my limbs
أحرر أحد أطرافي بعدها
Then the puzzle
وبعدها تركيب الأحجية
This feels like a mental game
تشبه لعبة ذكاء
Is it testing my intelligence?
رح يختبر ذكائي؟
I like this
أحب هذا النوع
I'm so bad at this
أنا سيء جداً
It burned my back
حرقت ظهري
Sunburned
حروق من الشمس
Sit back, sit back
اجلس مستنداً للخلف
If you don't lean back
لو ما تستند للخلف
I can't fully block the sun for you
ما رح أقدر أحميك من الشمس كلها
No, it's fine, let it be
لا بأس، هكذا جيد
Don't you feel even a bit cooler?
ما حسيت بأي انتعاش؟
Better not walk away
أفضل ألا تبتعد
Stand there and block
واقف هناك تمنع الشمس
Your posture is all wrong
طريقة وقوفكم خاطئة
Blocking the sunlight
تمنع أشعة الشمس
Bro, what are you guys thinking?
شباب، بماذا تفكرون؟
Such typical clueless straight guys
أنتم رجال بحق
Just keep stepping forward, nonstop
واقف للأمام فقط كل مرة
Hopelessly straight, absolutely hopeless
رجولة حديدية فعلاً
We're like his "left and right guardians"
أنا وهو حماة اليمين واليسار
Yeah
صح
Come on, let's raise our hands
هيا نرفع أيدينا
How about this
هكذا أفضل
Daniel
دانيال
What's going on?
ما الوضع؟
Sunshade
حماية من الشمس
You must be very happy
مبسوط أليس كذلك؟
Here, help me wipe it off
تعال امسح لي
Right side bangs
الغرة اليمنى
Wait
انتظر
Wait, fill the position
انتظر، غطي المكان
Fill the position
غطي المكان
Wipe your sweat
امسح العرق
It's okay
لا مشكلة
Let me wipe it for you
أمسح لك
Just like this, forward
بس إلى الأمام هكذا
There, that's enough
انتهينا، جيد الآن
Islanders, the Date Rights Competition
سكان الجزيرة، معركة حق المواعدة
"Love Breaks Barriers" is about to begin
قوة الحب ستكسر القيود قريباً
Your current location, islanders
أماكن سكان الجزيرة الحالية
is the activity zone
داخل منطقة الأنشطة
Your teammates are in the restricted zone
فرقكم في منطقة التقييد
and cannot move freely
لا يمكنهم التحرك بحرية
Activity zone islanders
سكان منطقة الأنشطة
must find all four matching keys
عليكم إيجاد المفاتيح الأربعة المطلوبة
to rescue your teammates
عندها فقط يمكنكم إنقاذ فرقكم
The first three keys are scattered
أول ثلاث مفاتيح موزعة على
throughout the activity zone
زوايا منطقة الأنشطة
Interesting
مثير للاهتمام
So we need to find the keys
يعني لازم نبحث عن المفاتيح
Find the keys
ابحث عن المفتاح
They might be in flower pots or under them
قد يكون تحت أصيص الزرع
Yes, underneath
صح، تحت في الأسفل
Or under that colored bucket
يمكن تحت سطل الألوان
Or maybe in that haystack
أو تحت كومة العشب
The fourth key
المفتاح الرابع
requires completing a double-sided puzzle
يجب حل أحجية الوجهين للحصول عليه
Restricted zone islanders
سكان منطقة التقييد
There's a double-sided puzzle before you
أمامكم أحجية وجهين
With your teammates' help
تحتاجون إلى مساعدة فريقكم
after freeing any body part
بعد تحرير أي جزء من الجسم
complete the puzzle challenge
عليكم إكمال تحدي الأحجية
After completing the puzzle
بعد إتمام الأحجية
collect the fourth key at the entrance
اذهبوا عند الباب لأخذ المفتاح الرابع
When all locks are opened
إذا فُتحت كل الأقفال
the shuttlecock challenge begins
يبدأ تحدي كرة الريشة
First team to complete five consecutively wins
أول فريق ينجز خمسة متتالية يفوز
Your final ranking determines
الترتيب النهائي لكل فريق سيحدد
whether you'll receive
هل ستكسبون
this round's dating invitation rights
دعوة المواعدة هذه الجولة
and choice of island supplies
واختيار الموارد داخل الجزيرة
We must win today
يجب أن نفوز اليوم
The Warrior Charging for Love
الأبطال لأجل الحب جاهزين
Are you ready?
هل أنت جاهز؟
Ready
جاهز
Where do you think the key is?
أين تعتقد المفتاح؟
Your call
أتبّعك
In the flowerpot
داخل أصيص الزرع
I've never dated Hu Wei before
عمري ما واعدت هو وي من قبل
I really want to win just once
أريد فعلاً الفوز مرة واحدة
First we find the key, right?
أولاً نبحث عن المفاتيح، صح؟
Find the key first
نبحث عن المفتاح أولاً
I've never won
ما ربحت أبداً
I wish I could have just once
أتمنى أن أحصل على فرصة واحدة
The right to choose someone myself
حقي في اختيار الشخص بنفسي
Sorry for the trouble
تعبتكم شوي
No trouble at all
لا تعب
Let's go for it
هيا، ابذلوا الجهد
If I win this dating opportunity
لو حصلت على حق المواعدة الآن
I'll choose Xiao Enya without hesitation
سأختار شاونيا بدون تردد
I like her the most right now
أنا أحبها أكثر الآن
Three
ثلاثة
You check the large items
أنت ابحث عن الأشياء الكبيرة
I'll search the ground
أنا أبحث في الأرض
Okay
تمام
Two
اثنان
I'll go there
سأذهب إلى هناك
One
واحد
Let's turn everything over
فتش كل شيء
You take this side, I'll take that side
هنا وهناك، كل الأماكن
Got it
حسنًا
Begin
ابدأوا!
Shugen, how do we find one?
جذور الأشجار، كيف نبحث؟
Not easy to find.
صعب العثور عليه
Might be inside the tire.
يمكن داخل العجلة
Is there any?
هل وجدتم؟
Never thought the key would be inside
لم أتوقع أن المفتاح وُضع بالداخل
Is this okay?
هل يمكن ذلك؟
It's open
انفتح
We can assemble it now
يمكننا البدء بالتجميع
We need to think about this
يجب أن نفكر قليلاً
This definitely isn't it
هذا بالتأكيد ليس هو
Let's try arranging them first
لنضعها كلها ونرى أولاً
This step is wrong
هذه الخطوة خاطئة
Did you find it?
هل وجدته؟
We didn't find it here.
لم أجد هنا
No.
لا
Nothing? How is that possible?
لا؟ كيف يمكن ألا يوجد!
Smart
ذكي
After one
تجاوزنا واحدة
One of you search, the other open
واحد يبحث، والآخر يفتح
One searches, one opens, right
واحد يبحث، وآخر يفتح، نعم
I think we should take all the keys first
أظن علينا أخذ جميع المفاتيح أولاً
One of you search, the other open
واحد يبحث، وآخر يفتح
Then I'll search
سأذهب للبحث إذاً
Okay
حسنًا
So hard to find
من الصعب جدًا إيجاده
Impressive
رائع
How come there's not a single one?
كيف لا يوجد واحد منهم؟
Jiang Shangru really is...
جيانغ شانغرو حقًا...
Pretty good
جيد جدًا
Don't compete with me
لا تنافسني عليه
Here it comes
وصلت
It's open
انفتح
Great
ممتاز
I've got one open
واحد عندي انفتح
Awesome
مذهل
He Jinyi is amazing, the best at finding keys
خه جين يي رائع، الأفضل في إيجاد المفاتيح
Okay
حسنًا
Do you want to exchange keys?
هل تريدون تبديل المفاتيح؟
Sure
ممكن
Let's swap one with you
دعونا نبدل معكم مفتاحًا
Great job, you're amazing
رائع، أنت حقًا رائع
So impressive
ممتاز للغاية
It's open
انفتح
Excellent
جيد
How could none of them work?
كيف يمكن ألا ينجح أي منها؟
We're still missing one.
ما زلنا بحاجة لمفتاح آخر
Right.
صحيح
So many pieces.
قطع كثيرة هكذا
What are we trying to assemble here?
ماذا سنركب من هذه القطع؟
No, this side's correct, but this side's wrong.
خطأ، هذه صحيحة، وتلك لا
Still missing one piece.
ينقصنا قطعة واحدة
This way looks correct to us.
بهذا الشكل يبدو لنا صحيحًا
Right.
صحيح
The backside - does it need to be correct on both sides?
الخلف، هل الوجهين كلاهما صحيح؟
Yes, both sides must match.
نعم، يجب أن يكونا صحيحين
This is too difficult.
هذا صعب جدًا
Matching both sides is really tough.
من الصعب ضبط الوجهين معًا
Wrong.
غير صحيح
I think it might be this piece?
أظن أنها هذه القطعة، صح؟
No good.
لا ينفع
We're done for.
انتهينا
Don't panic, stay calm.
لا تصرخ، لا تقلق
No, this piece is wrong, take it away.
خطأ، هذه ليست صحيحة، أزلها
This one's correct, right?
هذه صحيحة، أليس كذلك؟
No.
غير صحيح
It's wrong?
هل هي ليست صحيحة؟
Incorrect.
لا
Take a look at this one.
انظر إلى هذه
Yes, this one's correct.
صحيح، هذه صحيحة
Okay, alright, good.
تمام، جيد، جميل
That's it, let's follow this approach.
فليكن، نكمل بهذه الطريقة
Both sides need to match perfectly.
يجب أن يركب الوجهان معًا
Like this.
هكذا
During the puzzle assembly,
حين ترتيب القطع
Lu Wanfei solved the problem very quickly.
لو وانفاي حلت المسألة بسرعة
I genuinely thought at that time
حينها بالفعل شعرت
she was extremely calm and remarkably intelligent.
أنها هادئة جدًا وذكية للغاية
Correct.
صحيح
That's right.
تمام
This is it.
هذا هو الحل
Lift it up.
ارفَعْها
Blue team's front puzzle assembly is correct.
واجهة أحجية الفريق الأزرق صحيحة
Please flip the puzzle to check the backside.
يرجى قلب الأحجية على الخلف
Blue team's puzzle is correct
أحجية الفريق الأزرق صحيحة
Please collect the fourth key
يرجى استلام المفتاح الرابع
Okay
ممكن
Go get it
اذهب وخذها
Hurry
بسرعة
This one should definitely work
هذا المفتاح يجب أن يعمل
Because this is the final lock
لأن القفل الأخير هذا
Kick one to me
اركُل واحدة لي
No problem
لا بأس
Let's try again
حاول مرة أخرى
Kick it higher and straighter
اركُل أعلى وأكثر دقة
Take your time, we have plenty
خذ وقتك، لدينا الكثير من الوقت
No rush, take your time, we have plenty
لا بأس، خذ وقتك، لدينا وقت كافٍ
You kick the first one to me
اركُل الأول لي
Okay, that works
حسنًا، بخير
No
لا ينفع
That's too difficult
صعب جدًا هذا
Yes, connected
صحيح، متصل
Right
تمام
Smaller
أصغر قليلاً
Correct
صحيح
Two, three
اثنان، ثلاثة
Sorry
آسف
These two are correct
هاتان القطعتان صحيحتان
Right
صحيح
This side?
هذه الجهة؟
Is this correct?
هل هذا صحيح؟
This is wrong
هذا غير صحيح
This is wrong, take it away
هذه ليست صحيحة، أزلها
Is this the right way?
هكذا صحيح؟
Yes
نعم
Right, yes?
صحيح، أليس كذلك؟
Correct
تمام
Okay
حسنًا
You stay below and direct from behind
ابقَ بالأسفل ووجّهنا من الخلف
Okay, is this right?
حسنًا، هكذا صحيح؟
No
لا
No, okay
خطأ، حسنًا
Let's try a different one, okay?
نبدله إذن، ماذا ترون؟
How about this way?
وماذا عن هذا الشكل؟
That works, yes
ممكن، صحيح
Good, excellent
جيد جدًا، ممتاز
Yes, this is exactly the rhythm we want
صحيح، نحتاج هذا النوع من الإيقاع
Right
نعم
Come on, just like this
تعال، هكذا
See, our front side is all correct
انظر، كل الجهة الأمامية صحيحة
Okay
حسنًا
Please check it
يرجى مراجعتها
Is it correct?
هل هو صحيح؟
Purple team's puzzle front side is correct
واجهة أحجية الفريق البنفسجي صحيحة
Quick, go get the key
اذهب بسرعة وخذ المفتاح
Purple team's puzzle back side is incorrect
خلفية أحجية الفريق البنفسجي غير صحيحة
Please return and continue completing it
يرجى العودة والاستكمال
I might be too dumb, not very intelligent...
ربما أكون غبيًا، ذكائي ليس عاليًا
I figured it out.
لقد أنهيتُ التجميع
Okay, just one left, wait a moment.
جيد، بقيت قطعة، انتظروا قليلاً
I got it, keep going guys.
أنهيتُ التجميع، أكمِلوا أنتم
Wrong.
خطأ
Impressive.
رائع
Is there an eight in the middle here?
أليست هناك ثمانية هنا بالوسط؟
Is this side correct?
هل هذه الجهة صحيحة الآن؟
Let me try again.
لنبدل مرة أخرى
That was close.
يا له من خطر
I figured it out
أنا أنهيت التجميع
Have you seen this before?
هل راجعتم هذا؟
Yes, I have.
تمت المراجعة
We can check it again.
يمكنكم فحصها مرة أخرى
Keep it up, I've figured it out.
واصلوا أنتم، أنا أنهيتُ
Did you find it?
هل وجدتها؟
I've solved it
أنا أنهيت التجميع
Nice
جميل
It's open
انفتح
Hello
مرحبًا
Please flip the puzzle to the back
يرجى قلب الأحجية للخلف
Show him the reverse side
أرِه الوجه الآخر
Huang's team solved the puzzle correctly
أحجية الفريق الأصفر صحيحة
Right
صحيح
Get another key
خذوا مفتاحًا آخر
Come on
هيا! استمروا
Right foot
الرجل اليمنى
Try kicking the shuttlecock, hurry up
جربوا ركل الريشة بسرعة
Let me try
دعوني أجرب